<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ScrollAble List(Compose)</string>
    <string name="title1">Dark Chocolate</string>
    <string name="title2">Milk Chocolate</string>
    <string name="title3">White Chocolate</string>
    <string name="title4">Hazelnut Chocolate</string>
    <string name="title5">Mint Chocolate</string>
    <string name="description1">Dark chocolate is a form of chocolate made from cocoa solids, cocoa butter and sugar.
    It has a higher cocoa percentage than white chocolate, milk chocolate, and semisweet chocolate.</string>
    <string name="description2">Milk chocolate is a form of solid chocolate containing cocoa, sugar and milk.
    Milk chocolate contains smaller amounts of cocoa solids than dark chocolates do, and (as with white chocolate) contains milk solids.</string>
    <string name="description3">White chocolate is a chocolate made from cocoa butter, sugar and milk solids.
        It is ivory in color and lacks the dark appearance of most other types of chocolate as it does not contain the non-fat components of cocoa (cocoa solids).</string>
    <string name="description4">Hazelnut  chocolate adds a new dimension to the flavor by combining the flavor of chocolate with the distinctive hazelnut  nut.
    The hazelnut  provides a savory, crunchy, and slightly sweet touch that complements the richness of the chocolate.</string>
    <string name="description5">Mint chocolate (or chocolate mint) is a popular flavor of chocolate, made by adding a mint flavoring, such as peppermint, spearmint, or crème de menthe, to chocolate.
    Mint chocolate can be found in a wide variety of confectionery items, such as candy, mints, cookies, mint chocolate chip ice cream, hot chocolate, and others.</string>
    <string name="link1">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dark_chocolate</string>
    <string name="link2">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Milk_chocolate</string>
    <string name="link3">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/White_chocolate</string>
    <string name="link4">https://kioskcokelat.com/blogs/news/perbedaan-coklat-dan-coklat-hazelnut</string>
    <string name="link5">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chocolate#Flavors</string>
</resources>